+375 (29) 771-27-75

VLADIMIR MARKOV

FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

vladimir.v.markov@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/vladimir-markov github.com/web-steel

SUMMARY

Full-Stack Software Engineer with 9 years of experience in designing and implementing technical solutions and feature improvements for different projects, by using NodeJS, PHP, Go and React, as well as experience with SQL and NoSQL base. Capable of strong leadership and good organization to make sure every project is done on time.

EDUCATION

 Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics, Minsk (01.09.2010 – 30.06.2015):

```
faculty - "Computer systems and networks",
profession – "Computer Science",
specialization – "Banking systems",
qualification – "The mathematician-system programmer".
```

EXPERIENCE

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Big Data Technologies | 05/2018 - present

- Implementation of new features in the browser extension by using React
- Designing and developing a Telegram bot by using Laravel
- Designed and implemented RESTful services by using NodeJS
- Used Yii2 framework to customer portal websites
- Development and implementation of high-load services by using Go

• FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

LLC «ExonIT» | 05/2013 - 05/2018

• Design and development of web applications for analysis and GIS using Zend Framework and ExtJS.

SKILLS

Backend: NodeJS (Express, Koa2), PHP (Laravel, Yii, Zend), Go, Kafka,

Beanstalkd, Elasticsearch, Sphinx.

Fronend: React/Redux, Vue, Tailwind CSS, Webpack, Gulp.

Databases: MySQL, Clickhouse, MongoDB, Reids, PostgresSQL (PostGIS)

Infrastructure: AWS, DigitalOcean, Ansible, Gitlab CI, Docker.